{"data":[{"question":"Every country ________ a national flag.","a":"is","b":"are","c":"has","d":"have","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Subject (every country) is singular.\u00a0\n- To be: used to say that someone or something is the same as the subject of the sentence.\u00a0\n- To have: used to say what someone or something looks like, what qualities or features they possess.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Optical fibers ________ to deliver laser light.","a":"can also used","b":"also can use","c":"can also be used","d":"also can be used","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Passive voice with modal verb (can\/ could\/ will, may...): can\/ could\/ will\/may...+ be + PP \u00a0\n- Can also be used: is the right order.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"The flag of the original colonies may or may not have been ________ by Betsy Ross during the revolution.","a":"made","b":"make","c":"to make","d":"making","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Passive voice with may in present perfect: May+ have + been PP.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Goods for sale at ________ prices.","a":"attract","b":"attractive","c":"attraction","d":"attractively","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Adj stands before noun and modifies noun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Your mistakes in composition are similar ________ his.","a":"by","b":"to","c":"on","d":"with","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Be similar to sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Often a team of engineers is ________.","a":"work on one project","b":"on one project work","c":"working on one project","d":"to working on one project","answer":"3","explain":"\n- The present continuous with words such as \"always\" or \"constantly\" expresses the idea that something irritating or shocking often happens.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"A vacuum will neither conduct heat nor ________.","a":"transmit sound waves","b":"transmitting sound waves","c":"sound waves are transmitted","d":"the transmission of sound waves","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Neither + V+ O + Nor + V + O.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"To relieve pain caused by severe burns, prevent infection, and treat for shock, ________.","a":"taking immediate steps","b":"to take immediate steps","c":"taken steps immediately","d":"take immediate steps","answer":"4","explain":"\n- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"All the cereal grains ________ grow on the prairies and plains of the United States.","a":"but rice","b":"except the rice","c":"but for rice","d":"excepting rice","answer":"1","explain":"\n- But (+ noun\/verb) = Except.\u00a0\n- Except something from something.\u00a0\n- But for: used when you are saying that something would have happened if something or someone else had not prevented it.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"All of them are freshmen, ________ whom come from countryside.","a":"most of","b":"most","c":"both a and b are correct","d":"most of the","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Most of + Pronoun\/ definite noun.\u00a0\n- Most of the + definite noun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"}]}